<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yuhan Wei</title>
    <link>https://weiyh.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yuhan Wei</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://weiyh.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact 聯絡</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to drop me a line here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding Key Vision</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/wedding-key-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/wedding-key-vision/</guid>
      <description>Client: Pin &amp;amp; Andy Completed on: November 2020 Skills / Tools Used: Adobe Photoshop, Procreate  Design Concept 設計理念 Top 5 trees with well carbon sequestration in Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March For the Climate, Before It’s Too Late</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/2020-climate-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/2020-climate-march/</guid>
      <description>Client: Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition Completed on: September 2020 Skills / Tools Used: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator  響應今年全球「週五護未來」(Fridays for future) 行動，台灣青年氣候聯盟於 2020 年 9 月 27 日舉辦青年抗暖大遊行，提出對於國內氣候治理改革的「六大訴求、15 項行動」。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Change News Line Bot</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/climate-change-news-line-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/climate-change-news-line-bot/</guid>
      <description>Completed on: October 2019 Skills / Tools Used: Java, Spring Framework (Spring Boot, Spring Scheduler), LINE Messaging API  A LINE Bot which retrieves Google Alerts&#39; RSS feeds periodically (every hour) and sends feeds information to LINE user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Electric Scooters in Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/electric-scooters-in-taiwan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/electric-scooters-in-taiwan/</guid>
      <description>Client: Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition Completed on: July 2019 Skills / Tools Used: Microsoft PowerPoint  Infographics to introduce electric scooters in Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Green Transportation</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/introduction-to-green-transportation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/introduction-to-green-transportation/</guid>
      <description>Client: Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition Completed on: July 2019 Skills / Tools Used: Microsoft PowerPoint  Infographics to introduce green transportation in Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to NDC</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/introduction-to-ndc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/introduction-to-ndc/</guid>
      <description>Client: Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition Completed on: May 2019 Skills / Tools Used: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator Design with: Chia-Hsuan Ho  A series to introduce NDC (Nationally Determined Contribution), including the history of NDC (Nationally Determined Contribution), the current status of the world and Taiwan, how NDC works and what pirinciples it should follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TWYCC Facebook Covers</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/twycc-facebook-covers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/twycc-facebook-covers/</guid>
      <description>Client: Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition Completed on: January - March 2019 Skills / Tools Used: Microsoft PowerPoint, Adobe Photoshop  A collection of Facebook covers of Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition (TWYCC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Policy Fact Sheet</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/climate-policy-fact-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/climate-policy-fact-sheet/</guid>
      <description>Client: Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition Completed on: December 2018 Skills / Tools Used: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Indesign  To introduce Nationally Determined Contributions (NDC) and Talanoa dialogue into Taiwan, Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition (TWYCC) published Climate Policy Fact Sheet, aiming to let people know more about international climate policies, such as what role UNFCCC is playing, the importance of Paris Agreement, and the idea of Global Stocktake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COP Name Card</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/cop-name-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/cop-name-card/</guid>
      <description>Client: Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition Completed on: December 2018 Skills / Tools Used: Adobe Photoshop, Microsoft PowerPoint  This name card is for Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition (TWYCC) to use in the Conference of the Parties (COP) , to connect with participants in the conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COP23 Story Book</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/cop23-story-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/cop23-story-book/</guid>
      <description>Client: Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition Completed on: April 2018 Skills / Tools Used: Adobe Photoshop, Microsoft PowerPoint  Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition (TWYCC) collected and recorded stories and life with texts and photos during the 2017 Conference of the Parties (COP23) in Bonn, Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day Trip in Bali &amp; Tamsui</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/a-day-trip-in-bali-and-tamsui/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/a-day-trip-in-bali-and-tamsui/</guid>
      <description>Client: Taiwan Youth Climate Coalition Completed on: June 2018 Skills / Tools Used: Microsoft PowerPoint  A tourist map of Bali &amp;amp; Tamsui in New Taipei City and a tour guide of the green building New Taipei City Sustainable Development Education Center in Bali.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Envisioning Chinese Cinemas in the 21st Century</title>
      <link>https://weiyh.github.io/project/envisioning-chinese-cinemas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiyh.github.io/project/envisioning-chinese-cinemas/</guid>
      <description>Client: Department of Foreign Languages and Literatures, National Chiao Tung University Completed on: December 2013 Skills / Tools Used: Adobe Photoshop, Html, CSS, Javascript, PHP, Wordpress  The symposium “Chinese Cinemas in the 21st Century: Production, Consumption, Imagination” aims to promote new ways of thinking about the study of Chinese cinemas by bringing together established scholars into a dynamic network that crosses disciplinary boundaries; drawing expertise from film studies, media and communications, comparative literature, and cultural studies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
